<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Naruto Character List</string>
    <string name="about">About Me</string>
    <string name="character_name">Nama Character</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="faisal_reza_rahmat">Faisal Reza Rahmat</string>
    <string name="faisalrezarahmat1_gmail_com">faisalrezarahmat1@gmail.com</string>
    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Naruto Uzumaki</item>
        <item>Sasuke Uchiha</item>
        <item>Sakura Haruno</item>
        <item>Kakashi Hatake</item>
        <item>Hinata Hyuga</item>
        <item>Kiba Inuzuka</item>
        <item>Obito Uchiha</item>
        <item>Zetsu</item>
        <item>Itachi Uchiha</item>
        <item>Jiraya</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>Naruto Uzumaki yang bergelar Hokage Ketujuh adalah tokoh utama dari serial anime dan manga Naruto. Ia merupakan tokoh utama dalam serial ini. Ia digambarkan sebagai bocah berambut pirang dan bermata biru. Di pipinya ada semacam guratan yang mirip seperti kumis milik karakter Doraemon dalam manga Doraemon.</item>
        <item>Sasuke Uchiha adalah seorang karakter fiktif dari komik dan anime Naruto. Nama depan Sasuke, konon berasal dari nama seorang ninja legendaris, Sarutobi Sasuke. Sedangkan nama belakangnya, "Uchiha" dibaca sebagai "uchiwa", atau "kipas kertas"</item>
        <item>Sakura Haruno adalah tokoh fiksi dari serial manga dan anime Naruto. Ia merupakan seorang ninja wanita cantik yang tergabung dalam Tim 7 bersama Naruto Uzumaki dan Sasuke Uchiha di bawah bimbingan Kakashi Hatake. Ia juga merupakan seorang ninja medis di bawah bimbingan Tsunade Senju.Sakura Haruno adalah tokoh fiksi dari serial manga dan anime Naruto. Ia merupakan seorang ninja wanita cantik yang tergabung dalam Tim 7 bersama Naruto Uzumaki dan Sasuke Uchiha di bawah bimbingan Kakashi Hatake. Ia juga merupakan seorang ninja medis di bawah bimbingan Tsunade Senju.</item>
        <item>Kakashi Hatake adalah tokoh fiktif dalam serial manga dan anime Naruto. Ia merupakan Hokage Keenam dan juga guru dari Naruto, Sasuke, dan Sakura. Ia juga dikenal sebagai "Ninja Peniru" karena konon jumlah jurus yang sudah ia tiru mencapai seribu jurus.</item>
        <item>Hinata Hyuuga adalah tokoh fiksi dari seri anime dan manga Naruto karya Masashi Kishimoto. Hinata adalah salah satu keturunan dari klan Hyuuga. Ia memiliki seorang adik bernama Hanabi Hyuuga dan ayah bernama Hiashi Hyuuga. Saudara sepupunya bernama Neji Hyuuga</item>
        <item>Kiba Inuzuka adalah salah satu karakter dalam cerita fiksi dan manga Naruto. Inuzuka bisa diartikan "klan/perkumpulan anjing" yang dipakai sebagai salah satu nama klan yang cukup kuat pada zaman Edo.</item>
        <item>Uchiha Obito adalah karakter fiksi dalam manga Naruto. Dia adalah anggota klan Uchiha dari desa Konohagakure. Dia diyakini telah meninggal selama Perang Dunia Shinobi Ketiga, satu-satunya warisan yang masih hidup adalah Sharingan yang dia berikan kepada rekan setimnya, Kakashi Hatake.</item>
        <item>Zetsu Putih lahir dari Kaguya juga, meskipun tidak secara langsung sih. Ketika membuat Mugen Tsukuyomi, Kaguya menjebak setengah populasi Bumi dan menjadikan mereka pasukan Zetsu Putih. Salah satu dari mereka adalah Zetsu Putih utama yang di era modern bergabung dengan Zetsu Hitam di Akatsuki.</item>
        <item>Itachi Uchiha adalah karakter fiksi dalam serial manga dan anime Naruto. Ia merupakan kakak kandung dari Sasuke Uchiha dan seorang mantan ketua Anbu Konohagakure dari Klan Uchiha. Ia bertanggung jawab atas peristiwa Pembantaian Klan Uchiha yang telah membuatnya menjadi seorang ninja buronan tingkat S.</item>
        <item>Jiraiya adalah seorang karakter fiksi dari anime dan manga Naruto. Nama kanjinya memiliki arti "datang karena keinginan sendiri", yang banyak digambarkan oleh kelakuannya; datang dan menghilang dari desa Konoha secara tiba-tiba kapan saja ia mau.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_photo">
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/3/36/Naruto_Uzumaki.png</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/c/c6/Sasuke_Uchiha_%28Good%2CShippuden%29.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/2/2a/Sakura_Haruno.png</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/2/27/Kakashi_Hatake.png</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/c/c8/Hinata_Hyuga.png</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/2/22/Kiba_Inuzuka.png</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/3/31/Cosplay_of_Tobi_at_Collector%27s_Hub_Arena_Cosplay_2022.jpg/800px-Cosplay_of_Tobi_at_Collector%27s_Hub_Arena_Cosplay_2022.jpg</item>
        <item>https://d.wattpad.com/story_parts/241285992/images/14431bc581fac521.jpg</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/8/86/UItachi.png</item>
        <item>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/id/c/c9/Jiraiya_main.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="character_background">
        <item>Naruto was born on the night of October 10th to Minato Namikaze (the Fourth Hokage) and Kushina Uzumaki (the second jinchūriki of the Nine-Tails). He was named after Naruto Musasabi, the protagonist of Jiraiya\'s first book, which made the Sannin his godfather.[14] The Third Hokage made special arrangements for Minato to preserve Kushina\'s seal containing the Nine-Tails while she gave birth to Naruto in a remote location, assisted by midwives and Anbu. A masked man, Tobi, tracked down their location, however, killed the midwives and Anbu, and captured Naruto, forcing Minato to quickly rescue him and teleport him to a safe house.</item>
        <item>Sasuke is the second and youngest son of Mikoto and Fugaku Uchiha they named him after Sasuke Sarutobi in the hopes that he would someday be just as strong of a shinobi.[10] Sasuke grew up in the shadow of his older brother, Itachi, a natural prodigy who many in the Uchiha clan and the village would constantly compare Sasuke and any of his accomplishments to. Sasuke himself adored Itachi, never passing up an opportunity to spend time with him. Although Itachi welcomed his company, letting Sasuke watch him train and taking him on adventures into the forests,[11] Itachi in return rarely helped Sasuke himself become a better shinobi; when asked, he would often instead poke Sasuke\'s forehead and promise to do so some other time.</item>
        <item>Sakura is the only child of a civilian family. She had an healthy childhood, raised by her parents without any serious tragedy or complications, unlike her team members. When she entered Konoha\'s Academy, a few of the girls in her class started picking on her because of her broad forehead. Sakura tried to combat their teasing by hiding her forehead with her bangs, but this caused the girls to bully her even more. Ino Yamanaka, one of her classmates, saw this, and defended Sakura from her bullies and encouraged her to embrace her forehead rather than hide it.</item>
        <item>Kakashi was raised during his early years by his father, Sakumo. Sakumo was famed throughout the shinobi world, having saved Konoha on at least one occasion; Kakashi in particular revered his father. During one of Sakumo\'s missions after Kakashi was enrolled in Konoha\'s Ninja Academy - Sakumo made the decision to save the lives of his teammates rather than complete the assignment.</item>
        <item>Hinata is the oldest daughter of Hiashi Hyūga. When she was still a child, Hinata was almost kidnapped by the-then Head Ninja of Kumogakure, who was visiting Konoha under the guise of signing a peace treaty between their two villages. Hiashi killed him and saved Hinata, setting in motion the events that would become known as the "Hyūga Affair".</item>
        <item>At a very young age, Akamaru was given to Kiba by his mother, Tsume, and the two became very close soon afterwards. Before entering the Academy, Kiba and Akamaru played together a great deal, resulting in Tsume getting angry because they weren\'t training enough.[6] During Kiba\'s time at the Academy, he often cut class with Akamaru, stating that he wasn\'t suited to sit still at a desk, or otherwise getting into trouble, along with Chōji Akimichi, Shikamaru Nara, and Naruto Uzumaki. Together, these four would skip class and go to the practice hall (not to practice). They thought that it was fun to also test the patience of Iruka Umino, their Academy instructor. One day, Kiba fell asleep during class and, upon waking, saw Naruto attempting to use the Transformation Technique to turn into the Third Hokage for the first time, and failing twice. This caused Kiba to find Naruto incompetent, and he became among those who ridiculed him.</item>
        <item>Obito grew up not knowing who his parents were; in the anime, he was left in the care of his grandmother.[7] Feeling alone in the world, Obito dreamed of becoming Hokage so that the people of the village would acknowledge his existence.[8] He enrolled in the Academy to help him achieve that goal, where he developed a one-sided rivalry with Kakashi, whose natural talent and popularity he was jealous of. He also became a close friend of Rin Nohara, whom he eventually fell in love with. After finally graduating some years later, Obito, Rin, and Kakashi were placed on a team under the leadership of Minato Namikaze.[9]</item>
        <item>White Zetsu was originally one of the victims of Kaguya Ōtsutsuki\'s Infinite Tsukuyomi, who was transformed after being tethered to the God Tree over the course of years and ultimately stored within the Demonic Statue of the Outer Path. After Madara Uchiha summoned the statue and cultivated Hashirama Senju\'s DNA into a large flowering tree, Black Zetsu removed White Zetsu and the other victims from inside the husk, leading Madara to believe they were artificial humans created by the statue\'s chakra and Hashirama\'s DNA.[6][4] White Zetsu and other mutated humans were then tasked with intelligence gathering before he and a spiral-patterned Zetsu were entrusted with looking after the rehabilitating Obito Uchiha. Over time, the duo became friends with the young Uchiha.[</item>
        <item>Itachi was the first child born to Mikoto and Fugaku Uchiha. His early childhood was marked with violence: when he was four years old, the Third Shinobi World War waged and he witnessed first-hand many of the war\'s casualties. The death and destruction he experienced at such a young age traumatised Itachi and made him a pacifist,[6] leading to him training non-stop to achieve his dream of becoming a ninja among ninja in order to erase fighting from the world.[7] At age 5, after becoming a big brother to Sasuke, Itachi was approached by Shisui, who offered to train together. </item>
        <item>After he graduated from Konoha\'s Ninja Academy, Jiraiya was teamed with Orochimaru and Tsunade under the leadership of Hiruzen Sarutobi. Hiruzen gave them a bell test for the team\'s first exercise, during which Jiraiya repeatedly fell for Hiruzen\'s tricks, and for failing to acquire a bell, he was tied to a stump as punishment. Hiruzen encouraged Jiraiya to be more like Orochimaru, but Jiraiya countered that his Transparent Escape Technique was a fair testament to his skills, as he could spy on bathing women without getting caught: Hiruzen offered to accompany him to see if this was true.[8] Jiraiya had a certain interest in Tsunade from their first meeting,[9] and when her breasts developed, she became a frequent target of his peepings. She nearly killed him when she caught him on one occasion, forcing him to be more discreet about his interests.[10]</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>